# Ramsha Zahid

#### Contact

+91 9654428718

ryanaryme05@gmail.com

## **Educational Qualification**

- MA English (Hons) 2016-2018 Jamia Millia University
- M.A. in Sociology 2013- 2015 Ambedkar University Delhi
- B.A. (H) English 2010-2013 Kirorimal College, Delhi University
- Class XII 2010 Presentation Convent Sr. Sec. School
- Class X 2008
   Presentation Convent Sr. Sec. School

#### Skills

- Content Development
- Corporate Communications
- Brand Management
- Internal & External Communications
- Marketing Communications
- Canva Designing
- Microsoft Office
- CMS
- Social Media
- Decision Making
- Data Analysis
- Time Management
- Microsoft Office
- Team Management

### Summary

Highly seasoned and dedicated Corporate and Marketing Communications Specialist. Adept at facilitating clear and transparent communication between all levels of company staff. Able to work well independently or in coordination with a professional communications team.

### Work Experience

# Sr. Executive, , Marketing & Brand Communications

#### **Ikokas**

June 2022 - September 22

- Planned and executed Social media campaigns and calendars.
- Worked on website content for clients.
- Strategized to increase performance on LinkedIn and other social media platforms.
- Developed research based and SEO compatible website content (blogs) for target audience for Ikokas and its sister company Vector3.
- Copywriting & web content writing: in-house and clients.

# Deputy Manager, Enterprise Marketing Moglix

January 2022- April 2022

- Drove social media campaigns. .
- Managed 3 separate LinkedIn pages, including 1 fintech related.
- Connected with internal stakeholders for various marketing initiatives. .
- Performed quality check for social media content.
- Analyzed social media accounts performance on a weekly and monthly basis

#### Executive, Marketing Communications

Spire Research and Consulting October 2020 till January 2022

- Managed public relations.
- Fostered the new website launch.
- Drove Google Ads Campaigns and social media accounts.
- Developed brand marketing projects.
- Designed internal and external communications collateral for webinars, internal and external communications.
- Core contributer for leadership and employee branding campaigns.

## Languages known

English Hindi

Learning Korean and Bahasa

Indonesia

## References

Provided upon request.

# Assistant Executive, Marketing Communications

# Spire Research and Consulting November 2018 till September 2020

- Enabled execution of communication strategies.
- Created and published media and event coverages on the website.
- Facilitated digital marketing strategies.
- Developed social media marketing strategies.
- Monitored Google Ads and social media campaigns.
- Analyzed and compiled reports on website and campaigns performance through utilizing Google Analytics and more tools.
- Designed marketing collaterals and posters using Canva
- Point of contact for everything related to website management, from payments to maintanence..